Guide to the Neal Lane papers, 1998-2001, MS 502 MS 502
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series VII: Addendum
  - Talks, Conferences, and Summits
    - Rhodes/Marshalls Mock Interviews, 11/7/2012 (Box 104, Folder 53)
    - AWIS Meeting, 11/8/2012 (Box 104, Folder 54)
    - Philosophical Society of Texas Summit, 2/1/2013 (Box 104, Folder 55)
    - Oklahoma U. Physics, 2/8/2013 (Box 104, Folder 56)
    - Societal Convergence Report, 3/20/2013 (Box 104, Folder 57)
    - UIUC Physics Colloquium, 3/27/2013 (Box 104, Folder 58)
    - K21 Bill Press Intro, 4/4/2013 (Box 104, Folder 59)
    - Rorschach Memorial, 4/15/2013 (Box 104, Folder 60)
    - LEOH Talk, 4/25/2013 (Box 104, Folder 61)
    - NSF - NSB Dinner/Award, 5/9/2013 (Box 104, Folder 62)
    - Harte-HMNS Luncheon Talk, 5/9/2013 (Box 105, Folder 1)
    - Rosalind Franklin- Society Board Meeting, 12/19/2013 (Box 105, Folder 2)
    - ISMS Space Summit, 5/17/2013 (Box 105, Folder 3)
    - Climate Change Houston Tomorrow, 10/24/2013 (Box 105, Folder 4)
    - TAMU Climate: Dessler, 4/10/2014 (Box 105, Folder 5)
    - ISMS Space Talk, 6/6/2014 (Box 105, Folder 6)
    - Venky Bidav Symposium, 9/19-20/2014 (Box 105, Folder 7)
    - "Restoring Foundation" Report, Undated (Box 105, Folder 8)
    - Faulkner-Shakhashiri Dinner, 10/26/2014 (Box 105, Folder 9)
    - Chao Symposium (BRC), 10/27-28/2014 (Box 105, Folder 10)
    - Nei Meeting, National Graduate Institute for Political Studies- Japan, 12/5/2014 (Box 105, Folder 11)
    - AMS/MAA Panel, 1/12/2015 (Box 105, Folder 12)
    - Bienenstock Birthday, 3/20/2015 (Box 105, Folder 13)
    - Oklahoma U. Commencement, 5/8/2015 (Box 105, Folder 14)